<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CPI Converter</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_dev">About dev:\n\n\nAreeb Jamal (iamareebjamal) is a %d year old B.Tech student of AMU (Aligarh Muslim University) from India. He lives with his father, mother, and younger sister in Aligarh. He has been interested in technology since he gained senses. Before Android, he uses to gain knowledge about hacks of Windows PC and Java Mobiles, but those were nothing in comparison to what was to come.\n\nIn July 2012, his uncle gifted him Galaxy Ace-I GT-S5830i and though being grateful to him, its suckiness compelled him to join XDA on 7th August 2012, and he started exploring the oceans of knowledge on XDA.\n\nHe started creating themes at first, and then with help of some very gracious friends on XDA, started to learn more miscellaneous things such as bash, batch scripting, etc. He, from the beginning of 2013 started learning about app development and till mid 2014, he has released couple of apps and Xposed Modules.\n\nHe always shared his knowledge with others and was always more than eager to help people. After all, that\'s the motive of XDA, spreading the knowledge. His biggest contributions are, according to him, the guides, because teaching a man how to fish is always better that giving him a fish.\nHe currently is Recognised Contributor and Recognised Themer on XDA, and hopes to live up to those titles and prepare for gaining the third.\n\nLanguages he understands: \nJava(Android), Bash, Batch, C, XML, HTML, Edify, and easier ones like English, Hindi, Urdu, Pirate, etc\n\nSkills:\n&#8226; Photoshop\n&#8226; Dark, Satirical or Ironic humour\n&#8226; Android Development\n&#8226; Web Management\n&#8226; Can kill ants with a single finger, etc\n\nHobbies:\n&#8226; Staying inside room coding\n&#8226; Learning new languages(strictly programming ones)\n&#8226; App Designing\n&#8226; Trying new things on Android\n&#8226; Fighting off iPhone and Samsung users on internet\n&#8226; Teasing sister\n&#8226; Knowing about universe and physics\n&#8226; Cursing random scientists and mathematicians\n&#8226; Praising Faraday, Einstein, Hawkings and other off the hook crazy brainy geeks\n&#8226; Knowing more about universe\n&#8226; Trying to understand life\n&#8226; Wanting to know what is inside black-hole without inspecting it personally\n&#8226; Trying to understand woman(I know I shouldn\'t even dare!)\n&#8226; Knowing more about universe, etc\n\nDislikes:\n&#8226; Fly in coffee\n&#8226; Bugs(Both real and computer)\n&#8226; Media Transfer Protocol(Mass Storage FTW!)\n&#8226; Turbo C\n&#8226; Chemistry\n&#8226; Apple(not fruit)\n&#8226; Samsung, Touchwiz, other related items\n&#8226; Slow Interenet Connection\n&#8226; Partial Teachers\n&#8226; WiFi Passwords\n&#8226; Blue Screen of Death\n&#8226; NullPointerException, etc</string>

</resources>
